<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Information Book</string>
    <string name="united_kingdom">
        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t:London \n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t: London \n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: English \n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 243,610 km² \n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: GBP \n\n

        \t\t The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain,[k][14] is a country in Europe, off the north-western coast of the continental mainland.[15] It comprises England, Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland.[16] The United Kingdom includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland, and many smaller islands within the British Isles.[17] Northern Ireland shares a land border with the Republic of Ireland; otherwise, the United Kingdom is surrounded by the Atlantic Ocean, the North Sea, the English Channel, the Celtic Sea and the Irish Sea. The total area of the United Kingdom is 242,495 square kilometres (93,628 sq mi), with an estimated 2020 population of more than 67 million people.[18]

\n\n\t\tThe United Kingdom has evolved from a series of annexations, unions and separations of constituent countries over several hundred years. The Treaty of Union between the Kingdom of England (which included Wales, annexed in 1542) and the Kingdom of Scotland in 1707 formed the Kingdom of Great Britain. Its union in 1801 with the Kingdom of Ireland created the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland. Most of Ireland seceded from the UK in 1922, leaving the present United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, which formally adopted that name in 1927.[l] The nearby Isle of Man, Guernsey and Jersey are not part of the UK, being Crown Dependencies with the British Government responsible for defence and international representation.[19] There are also 14 British Overseas Territories,[20] the last remnants of the British Empire which, at its height in the 1920s, encompassed almost a quarter of the world\'s landmass and a third of the world\'s population, and was the largest empire in history. British influence can be observed in the language, culture and the legal and political systems of many of its former colonies.[21][22]

\n\n\t\tThe United Kingdom is a constitutional monarchy and parliamentary democracy.[m][24] The capital and largest city is London, a global city and financial centre with a metropolitan area population of over 14 million. Other major cities include Birmingham, Manchester, Glasgow, Liverpool and Leeds.[25] Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland have their own devolved governments, each with varying powers.[26] The UK became the world\'s first industrialised country and was the world\'s foremost power during the 19th and early 20th centuries.[27] In the 21st century, the UK retains considerable economic, cultural, military, scientific, technological and political influence.[28] The United Kingdom has the world\'s sixth-largest economy by nominal gross domestic product (GDP), and the eighth-largest by purchasing power parity. It has a high-income economy and a very high Human Development Index rating, ranking 18th in the world. It also performs well in international rankings of education, healthcare, life expectancy and human development.[29] It is a recognised nuclear state and is ranked fourth globally in military expenditure.[30] It has been a permanent member of the United Nations Security Council since its first session in 1946.

\n\n\t\tThe United Kingdom is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations, the Council of Europe, the G7, the Group of Ten, the G20, Five Eyes, the United Nations, NATO, AUKUS, the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD), Interpol, and the World Trade Organization (WTO). It was a member state of the European Communities (EC) and its successor, the European Union (EU), from its accession in 1973 until its withdrawal in 2020 following a referendum held in 2016.
    </string>
    <string name="france">
        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t:Paris \n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t: Arles \n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: French \n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 549,087 km² \n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Euro \n\n

        \t\tFrance, officially the French Republic (French: République française [ʁepyblik frɑ̃sɛz]),[14] is a country primarily located in Western Europe. It also comprises of overseas regions and territories in the Americas and the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian Oceans.[XII] Its metropolitan area extends from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean and from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea; overseas territories include French Guiana in South America, Saint Pierre and Miquelon in the North Atlantic, the French West Indies, and many islands in Oceania and the Indian Ocean. Due to its several coastal territories, France has the largest exclusive economic zone in the world. France borders Belgium, Luxembourg, Germany, Switzerland, Monaco, Italy, Andorra, and Spain in continental Europe, as well as the Netherlands, Suriname, and Brazil in the Americas via its overseas territories in French Guiana and Saint Martin. Its eighteen integral regions (five of which are overseas) span a combined area of 643,801 km2 (248,573 sq mi) and contain close to 68 million people (as of July 2022).[5][8] France is a unitary semi-presidential republic with its capital in Paris, the country\'s largest city and main cultural and commercial centre; other major urban areas include Marseille, Lyon, Toulouse, Lille, Bordeaux, and Nice.

\n\n\t\tInhabited since the Palaeolithic era, the territory of Metropolitan France was settled by Celtic tribes known as Gauls during the Iron Age. Rome annexed the area in 51 BC, leading to a distinct Gallo-Roman culture that laid the foundation of the French language. The Germanic Franks formed the Kingdom of Francia, which became the heartland of the Carolingian Empire. The Treaty of Verdun of 843 partitioned the empire, with West Francia becoming the Kingdom of France in 987. In the High Middle Ages, France was a powerful but highly decentralised feudal kingdom. Philip II successfully strengthened royal power and defeated his rivals to double the size of the crown lands; by the end of his reign, France had emerged as the most powerful state in Europe. From the mid-14th to the mid-15th century, France was plunged into a series of dynastic conflicts involving England, collectively known as the Hundred Years\' War, and a distinct French identity emerged as a result. The French Renaissance saw art and culture flourish, conflict with the House of Habsburg, and the establishment of a global colonial empire, which by the 20th century would become the second-largest in the world.[15] The second half of the 16th century was dominated by religious civil wars between Catholics and Huguenots that severely weakened the country. France again emerged as Europe\'s dominant power in the 17th century under Louis XIV following the Thirty Years\' War.[16] Inadequate economic policies, inequitable taxes and frequent wars (notably a defeat in the Seven Years\' War and costly involvement in the American War of Independence) left the kingdom in a precarious economic situation by the end of the 18th century. This precipitated the French Revolution of 1789, which overthrew the Ancien Régime and produced the Declaration of the Rights of Man, which expresses the nation\'s ideals to this day.

\n\n\t\tFrance reached its political and military zenith in the early 19th century under Napoleon Bonaparte, subjugating much of continental Europe and establishing the First French Empire. The French Revolutionary and Napoleonic Wars shaped the course of European and world history. The collapse of the empire initiated a period of relative decline, in which France endured a tumultuous succession of governments until the founding of the French Third Republic during the Franco-Prussian War in 1870. Subsequent decades saw a period of optimism, cultural and scientific flourishing, as well as economic prosperity, known as the Belle Époque. France was one of the major participants of World War I, from which it emerged victorious at a great human and economic cost. It was among the Allied powers of World War II but was soon occupied by the Axis in 1940. Following liberation in 1944, the short-lived Fourth Republic was established and later dissolved in the course of the Algerian War. The current Fifth Republic was formed in 1958 by Charles de Gaulle. Algeria and most French colonies became independent in the 1960s, with the majority retaining close economic and military ties with France.

\n\n\t\tFrance retains its centuries-long status as a global centre of art, science and philosophy. It hosts the fifth-largest number of UNESCO World Heritage Sites and is the world\'s leading tourist destination, receiving over 89 million foreign visitors in 2018.[17] France is a developed country ranked 28th in the Human Development Index, with the world\'s seventh-largest economy by nominal GDP and tenth-largest by PPP; in terms of aggregate household wealth, it ranks fourth in the world.[18] France performs well in international rankings of education, health care, and life expectancy. It remains a great power in global affairs,[19] being one of the five permanent members of the United Nations Security Council and an official nuclear-weapon state. France is a founding and leading member of the European Union and the Eurozone,[20] as well as a key member of the Group of Seven, North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) and Francophonie.



    </string>
    <string name="italy">
        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t:Rome \n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t: Rome \n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: Italian \n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 301,340 km² \n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Euro \n\n

        \t\tItaly , officially the Italian Republic,[a] or the Republic of Italy,[13][14] is a country in Southern Europe.[15][16][17] It is located in the middle of the Mediterranean Sea, and its territory largely coincides with the homonymous geographical region.[18] Italy is also considered part of Western Europe,[19][note 1] and shares land borders with France, Switzerland, Austria, Slovenia and the enclaved microstates of Vatican City and San Marino. It has a territorial exclave in Switzerland, Campione. Italy covers an area of 301,230 km2 (116,310 sq mi), with a population of over 60 million.[20][21] It is the third-most populous member state of the European Union, the sixth-most populous country in Europe, and the tenth-largest country in the continent by land area. Italy\'s capital and largest city is Rome.

\n\n\t\tItaly was the native place of many civilizations such as the Italic peoples and the Etruscans, while due to its central geographic location in Southern Europe and the Mediterranean, the country has also historically been home to myriad peoples and cultures, who immigrated to the peninsula throughout history.[22][23] The Latins, native of central Italy, formed the Roman Kingdom in the 8th century BC, which eventually became a republic with a government of the Senate and the People. The Roman Republic initially conquered and assimilated its neighbours on the Italian peninsula, eventually expanding and conquering parts of Europe, North Africa and Asia. By the first century BC, the Roman Empire emerged as the dominant power in the Mediterranean Basin and became a leading cultural, political and religious centre, inaugurating the Pax Romana, a period of more than 200 years during which Italy\'s law, technology, economy, art, and literature developed.[24][25]

\n\n\t\tDuring the Early Middle Ages, Italy endured the fall of the Western Roman Empire and the Barbarian Invasions, but by the 11th century, numerous city-states and maritime republics, mostly in the North, became prosperous through trade, commerce, and banking, laying the groundwork for modern capitalism.[26][27] The Renaissance began in Italy and spread to the rest of Europe, bringing a renewed interest in humanism, science, exploration, and art. During the Middle Ages, Italian explorers discovered new routes to the Far East and the New World, helping to usher in the European Age of Discovery. Italy\'s commercial and political power significantly waned with the opening of trade routes that bypassed the Mediterranean.[28] Centuries of rivalry and infighting between the Italian city-states, and the invasions of other European powers during the Italian Wars of the 15th and 16th centuries, left parts of Italy politically fragmented.[29][30]

\n\n\t\tBy the mid-19th century, rising Italian nationalism, along with other social, economic, and military events, led to a period of revolutionary political upheaval.[31] After centuries of political and territorial divisions, Italy was almost entirely unified in 1861 following a war of independence, establishing the Kingdom of Italy.[32] From the late 19th century to the early 20th century, Italy rapidly industrialised, mainly in the north, and acquired a colonial empire,[33] while the south remained largely impoverished and excluded from industrialisation, fuelling a large and influential diaspora.[34] Despite being one of the victorious allied powers in World War I, Italy entered a period of economic crisis and social turmoil, leading to the rise of the Italian fascist dictatorship in 1922. The participation of Fascist Italy in World War II on the Axis side ended in military defeat. Following the rise of the Italian Resistance and the subsequent Italian Civil War and liberation of Italy, the country abolished its monarchy, established a democratic unitary parliamentary republic, enjoyed a prolonged economic boom, and became a highly developed country.[35]

\n\n\t\tItaly has an advanced economy, being the tenth-largest nominal GDP (third in the European Union) in the world, the ninth-largest by national wealth and the third-largest by central bank gold reserve. It ranks highly in life expectancy, quality of life,[36] healthcare,[37] and education. The country is a great power, and it has a significant role in regional[38][39] and global[40][41] economic, military, cultural, and diplomatic affairs. Italy is a founding and leading member of the European Union and a member of numerous international institutions, including the United Nations, NATO, the OECD, the G7, the Latin Union, the Schengen Area, and many more. The source of many inventions and discoveries, the country is considered a cultural superpower[42] and has long been a global centre of art, music, literature, philosophy, science and technology, tourism and fashion, as well as having greatly influenced and contributed to diverse fields including cinema, cuisine, sports, jurisprudence, banking, and business.[43] It has the world\'s largest number of World Heritage Sites (58), and is the world\'s fifth-most visited country.



    </string>
</resources>